[indistinct conversations,
police radio chatter]
[Cho]
The attack took place
in the middle of a shift change.
Normally the shift
works till morning,
but some of the crew
had a bachelor party tonight.
Who's getting married?
Toby Rawlins.
He found the victim seconds
after his throat was cut.
Mm. That's gotta be
the worst bachelor party ever.
[Teresa]
'Did toby see what happened?'
He saw a hooded man
run into the woods.
Jeans, dark jacket.
Couldn't make out a face.
Any sign of a murder weapon?
Nothing.
- Who's the victim?
- Paul Satterfield.
25 years on the job,
multiple citations for bravery.
It's not your fault.
Yeah, I know that.
Unless, of course,
you did it.
- Did you kill him?
- No!
Okay.
Just had to ask.
What are you doing
out here, anyway?
Don't you have to celebrate
your last day of freedom?
Paul couldn't make the party.
He never leaves
his shift early.
But he bought me a cigar
for us to smoke together.
So someone knew the victim
was coming out here?
If you're saying one of
our guys did this, no way.
I saw the killer
get away through there.
Look, we had half the fire
station looking for him.
Guys from two shifts.
Could be the killer
circled back around
and joined the search
for himself.
Could have happened. It would
have been chaotic out here.
Paul Satterfield
was one of us.
We all loved him
like a brother.
Yeah. You've heard of
Cain and Abel, right?
Cho, gather the firefighters.
We need to establish a timeline.
Can I borrow
your flashlight?
I'm gonna go looking
for the murder weapon.
[crickets chirping]
[howling in distance]
Aah!
[grunting]
[choking]
Jane?
Jane, you out here?
Jane, come on!
No.
Paramedics!
I need help now!
Please!
[theme music]
[male #1]
Still not breathing.
No pulse.
- Is he prone to seizures?
- No.
How long has he
been out here?
I don't know.
Um, seven, eight minutes, maybe.
- Defibrillator, standing by.
- Clear.
Please.
[indistinct chattering]
Everybody clear.
[pops loudly]
Still nothing.
Clear.
[pops loudly]
[gags]
- Jane... Jane, are you okay?
- Got a rhythm.
Bring that O2 up.
Can you hear me? Jane?
Get him ready
for transport.
On my count.
One, two, three, lift.
- Coming through.
- Hey, watch yourselves.
Make a hole, make a hole.
Coming through.
How is he?
He's breathing.
He's gonna be fine.
He'll be fine.
[monitor beeping steadily]
Jane?
How you feeling?
Excellent, I think.
It's good to see
you breathing.
It's good to
see you, period.
We're doing everything we can
to find your attacker.
You didn't happen
to see a face, did you?
No.
Not that I can remember.
What's the last thing
you do remember?
Are we sleeping together?
Excuse me?
Well, you're a cop,
that's obvious
but you're not treating me
like a suspect.
And I can't see any other
reason for a police officer
to come to my bedside
unless we're--
Unless we're
sleeping together.
You don't know who I am?
Please don't take it personally.
I'm sure you're quite memorable.
I just, I've been
through a lot..
...apparently.
No.
We are not
sleeping together.
We're working toward it,
though, right?
So I haven't
missed anything?
What's your name?
Are you putting me on?
I wish I was.
Um, I'm Teresa Lisbon
with the CBI.
I'm a homicide detective.
You're my consultant.
I catch bad guys?
Wow, that sounds like fun.
I always wanted to pit
my psychic skills
against criminals.
You're not a psychic.
You used to pretend
to be one, but--
But what?
Teresa?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I should have talked to the
doctor before I came here. I--
Whoa, whoa.
Teresa, wait.
I saw something
during my attack.
What did you see?
A light.
What kind of light?
White light.
Intensely bright.
And I walked toward it.
There were people, lots of
people gathered around
reaching out
with their hands to me.
There was a woman--
A woman who knew you.
Your mother.
Jane, I'm not impressed.
I told you my mother
died when I was a girl.
Well, did you tell me
that she gave you that cross?
You touched it just like that
when I was unconscious.
It's what led her to me.
'And now I can
lead her to you.'
You wanna put me in touch
with my dead mother?
I'm a psychic, Teresa.
That's what I do.
- He doesn't know me.
- He doesn't know who he is.
It's called
dissociative fugue--
the temporary loss
of personal identity.
It can last hours, months,
and in rare cases, years.
But he remembers
some things
like he used to be
a fake psychic.
He did a reading on me,
it was a good one.
Has he had any
previous traumas?
His wife and daughter
were murdered.
There you go. His subconscious
mind is protecting itself
from further trauma
by blocking out that pain.
As far as Patrick knows,
his family never existed.
Their death is what
brought him to us.
And that's why
he doesn't know you.
But you're just
what he needs
to get back on his feet.
- How should we act?
- Normal.
I never know how to act
around Jane normally.
Then you're all set.
Don't talk about his past.
It's important that his memories
come back on their own.
He should still
be in the hospital.
The doctor wants him
in a familiar environment.
Is he gonna help
with the case?
He says he can't wait.
- You sure this is a good idea?
- I don't know.
Jane needs something to hold on
to and we're gonna be there.
Where are we with the victim?
According to his co-workers
Paul Satterfield
was a legend.
The old guard respected him,
the younger guys idolized him.
Satterfield left behind
a widow, Diane.
They were together
for 16 years.
She's coming by to talk.
- Anything from the crime scene?
- No trace evidence.
All the EMT'S
and firefighters
trying to rescue him,
they contaminated everything.
Okay, I vote we skip
the awkward introductions
because you all know me,
and in one glance
I know the same about you
as the day I forgot you.
You gave us
a scare yesterday.
Well, not my intention,
I assure you.
Well, we're just glad
you pulled through.
Thanks, Bigsby.
Rigsby.
It's Wayne Rigsby.
Wayne.
We're just working the case,
so feel free to jump in anytime.
Okay. Your armed robber--
desperate amateur.
Why work alone?
Because he doesn't know
any other criminals.
The Lucha Libremask
projects the correct attitude.
But look..
Look what he is wearing.
- Khakis and a fitted sweater.
- Jane--
No wonder the guard
tried to shoot him.
The closest a man
should ever come
to touching it is helping
a woman out of one.
Jane, another team is
handling the ATM lobby hit.
We got the dead fireman.
Got it.
[Cho]
'The victim was featured
in a local newscast'
'the day of his murder.'
I pulled a copy.
We might find
something useful in it.
[male on TV]
'A dramatic rescue
before the light of dawn'
'firefighter Paul Satterfield
risked it all'
'to pull an unconscious man from
his burning house in Wilton.'
'Both men barely escaped
with their lives'
'when a dramatic flashover
exploded behind them.'
'Officials believe the fire
spread from the chimney'
'of a two-story home
in Wilton.'
'was treated
for smoke inhalation'
'and released
from the hospital.'
'This isn't the first time we've
featured Paul Satterfield'
'on this news cast...'
Where's Satterfield's partner?
You always enter a burning
structure with two firefighters.
Who led the victim
into that death trap alone.?
Go and find out.
Take Jane.
Me?
Whoever killed Satterfield
tried to kill you.
Oh, you wanna give him
another try at that?
You'll be okay.
Rigsby will be with you.
Why is Teresa insisting that
I meet these firefighters?
Well, you might
recognize the killer.
Well, it's doubtful.
I was attacked in the dark
and held underwater.
Isn't it likely that
he took me from behind?
Yeah, probably.
But you're still good
at sussing out guilty parties.
Huh.
How do I do that exactly?
Uh, it's hard to say.
Causing trouble, mostly.
And you don't mind?
No, we're a team.
We help each other out.
Oh.
Well, in that case, Wayne,
what's the best way in
with the luscious redhead?
Van Pelt?
Clearly you two had a thing,
and she dumped you
but maybe you can share a tip
on how to open the cookie jar.
Get some, uh..
...tasty gingersnaps?
Oh.
You want a tip?
[elevator bell dings]
Back off.
I thought we
were a team.
I'm sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Satterfield.
- You are, are you?
- Yes, ma'am.
I hold firefighters
in the highest regard.
Even ones who die
in a knife fight?
Hell, even I didn't see
that one coming.
Oh. You mind?
It's not allowed.
Did your husband
have any enemies?
God, no.
Paul Satterfield was a hero.
You didn't hear?
You will.
Where's your wedding ring?
Oh, I'm having it
melted for cash.
No, not really.
At least not for cash anyway.
Having it resized
to fit my middle finger.
Think of it
as a statement.
Clearly you don't mind being
considered a murder suspect.
Consider me
whatever you want.
You know?
You're wasting your time.
I was working last night.
Yeah? Where?
Suicide prevention hotline.
It's true.
Two minutes with me
and your life
ain't looking so bad.
You sure I can't
have a smoke?
[indistinct conversations]
Gather around, please.
These men are with CBI.
We're gonna do everything we can
to help them out for Paul.
Thank you, captain.
My name is Agent Rigsby.
This is Patrick Jane.
I know that you're here
today are on your day off
and I wanna thank
you all for coming.
I spent a lot of time
working arson
which is why I know
that Paul Satterfield
was hung out to dry yesterday
during that house fire.
- What are you suggesting?
- Doesn't matter.
- I got what I need.
- You recognize the killer?
No, but I've seen enough
to identify the killer.
Or, more specifically
your mascot here
has smelled enough.
- What's his name?
- Hoser.
Naturally. Uh, may I?
Sure.
Come on, Hoser.
We've all heard of dogs
that have found their way home
from thousands of miles away.
That's because these animals
have a sixth sense.
Natural disasters,
the presence of spirits
some of them can even
detect cancer.
- That's a bunch of crap.
- Really?
An Atlanta woman
credits her dog Floyd Henry
for pawing a cancerous tumor
which saved her life.
Why do I remember that?
In any case, on my command,
our canine friend here
will use his
extrasensory perception
to sniff out
a killer's guilt.
And I do believe
he's found it.
Hoser, go get the killer.
- Huh.
- Hey.
- What's this?
- Smoked kipper.
Also known as red herring.
[laughing]
I found it in your kitchen.
[chuckling]
What?
What's not funny?
What's going on here?
You said I cause trouble.
Yeah, to help
the investigation.
That guy's the paramedic
that saved your life.
- Oh, well, thank you very much.
- No problem.
- Are we done here?
- Not by a mile.
When Hoser here was, uh,
pouncing on my rescuer
I couldn't help but notice
a profound sense of relief
from..
...you, sir.
What's your relationship
with the deceased?
Um, not much.
No sad feelings,
no wedding ring.
[sniffs]
That's ladies' perfume
with a top note of orange
mixed with bitter almond.
That's not a young
woman's fragrance.
Were you sleeping
with the victim's wife?
That's offensive.
Firefighters are a brotherhood.
Wives are off-limits.
Well, tell him that.
It's time
for you to go.
Huh, Larkin?
- It's time for you to go.
- It's okay, cap.
It's all gonna
come out anyway.
What he said is true.
I was having an affair
with Paul's wife.
How was that?
Yeah.
Just like the old you.
Heard you riled 'em up
in there.
Sounds like
the Jane I know.
Hmm.
Is anything coming
back to you?
Kids prefer cheese
over fried green spinach.
[chuckling]
Come again?
It's an acronym for
the seven levels of taxonomy.
Kingdom, phylum,
class, order
family, genus,
species.
Impressive.
I can also name
the geological time periods
the world's longest rivers
by size
and the complete
works of Shakespeare
in chronological order.
So the memory palace
is intact.
I told you
about the memory palace?
We're friends.
The doctor says it's
your emotional memories
that are tripping you up.
Has anything
come back to you?
Anything at all?
No.
What do you remember
about this?
My wedding ring?
No better way
to gain a woman's trust
than to wear a wedding ring,
except maybe buy a dog.
Okay, so you wear a wedding ring
to get over on women?
Worked on you.
You remember the house fire
that we saw on the newscast?
It was the only call
that the victim responded to
the day that
he was murdered.
I'm gonna have Cho
look at the house.
Go with him.
It's his turn
to babysit me now?
Well, somebody has to.
Pleasant weather.
Has it been like
this all week?
I guess. Why?
Big elephants can always
understand small elephants
because, Teresa, because.
Oh. Oh, I get it.
It's another acronym.
Mm.
Were you at the firehouse
the night the victim
was murdered?
I left early to go
to the bachelor party.
Were you with anyone?
No.
So you could have
circled back?
I could have,
but I didn't.
Why were you sleeping
with Mrs. Satterfield?
It felt good.
Good enough to want
her husband dead?
I didn't want him dead.
Oh, no?
Well, I checked
yesterday's logs.
You were
Satterfield's partner.
You let him go upstairs
without backup, alone.
I was the one who was
left without backup, okay?
We live and dieby SOG's.
do you know what those are?
Standard operating guidelines.
Yeah.
And we were conducting
a standard left-hand search
of a fully involved house
when Paul decides to run
upstairs and find the homeowner.
Why didn't you go with him?
He left me in a smoke-filled
room with zero visibility.
I couldn't see my hand
in front of my face
much less
which way he ran.
That's the way it was
with Paul.
He could break
every rule
leave his
partner in danger
and still
he's the hero.
So why didn't you
tell the captain?
Paul was good press.
Look, I feel bad
that he's gone.
But I'll tell you what.
I'm glad that I don't
have to count on him
to cover my back
at the next fire.
You take this side
of the street.
Find out if the neighbors
saw the victim
interacting with anyone
suspicious during the fire.
You want me to go
door to door?
You do it all the time.
It's one of the more
interesting things
about being a consultant.
[chuckling]
You're a clever one,
Mr. Cho.
And I'll do your bidding
but first I wanna take a look
at this burned-out house.
When can I go inside?
I need to get in there.
CBI.
What's going on here?
They won't let me
inside my house.
It's a standard
arson investigation.
- We'll call him when it's over.
- This is crazy.
Why would I
set fire to my house?
Everything is in there.
- My kid's childhood--
- No one's accusing you, sir.
I know you.
I saw you on the TV.
The fireman saved your life.
Patrick Jane.
Yeah. Tom Wilcox.
I almost died yesterday, too,
but, uh, no news cameras.
Did you know the man
who saved you was killed?
Yeah, I read it
in the paper.
I didn't get a chance
to thank him.
Did you see the victim
in conflict with anyone?
No, I was unconscious
the whole time.
Me, too. The guy put
my head under the water.
How did you black out?
When the fire
jumped the fireplace
I ran upstairs and grabbed
all the valuables that I could
but the smoke was too thick,
and I couldn't breathe.
Well, we both
cheated death.
That, that's just..
That's remarkable.
You know, we should
get t-shirts made up.
Well, I'm glad
that you're happy
but I lost
everything that I own.
I got my wife and my daughter
in a motel I can't afford.
Nothing but the clothes
on our backs.
You can ask your insurance
company for an advance?
My house isn't insured.
I mean it was, but..
I'm a savings
and loan officer
and ever since
the banks collapsed
I've been out of work.
Okay. Well, let's forget
about the t-shirts, then.
Mr. Cho, let's say we give
this poor man a ride back.
Come on.
- Okay, thanks.
- Hey, boss?
On Rigsby's advice,
I went through
Mrs. Satterfield's
credit reports.
Take a look at this.
Looks like our grieving widow
had a lot to celebrate.
Yeah.
I'm thinking about using
that life insurance money
to redo my kitchen.
No offense, Mrs. Satterfield,
but you're quite brazen.
Which means you're either
innocent or stupid.
Well, she doubled down on her
husband's life insurance policy
a month before his murder.
I'm going with stupid.
Wouldn't be the first time
a cheating wife
arranged for
her husband's death.
You think I was unfaithful?
You were sleeping
with another man.
Paul knew about my affair.
Truth is, he was relieved.
I stopped begging
for his attention.
He could never
give me what I wanted.
- Which was?
- A marriage.
He left ours years ago.
My husband was a junkie.
- Heroin?
- Adrenaline.
Couldn't get enough of it.
Drinking in all that glory
dancing in the fire.
How do you compete with
the high of being a hero?
Why didn't you just leave him?
And what kind of a settlement
am I gonna get
from a firefighter?
I upped the policy because his
death was just a matter of time.
Every day, a race towards
the edge of a cliff.
I bet getting stabbed was
the biggest rush of his life.
Thanks for the ride.
It's, uh, it's been
a tough day.
Hi, dad!
Hey, baby.
Who are your friends?
I'm Agent Cho.
This is Patrick Jane.
We're investigating the murder
of Paul Satterfield.
I was just reading
about him in the paper.
'So sad.'
'Lulu would be without
a father right now'
'if it weren't for him.'
Do you know anything
about the funeral?
Uh, we'd like to be there.
Well, they usually have that
information in the story.
Let me have a look here.
Oh, this clown again.
He's stealing a lot of press
from our fallen hero.
Did you find my dolls?
I'm afraid not, honey.
I still haven't been able
to get inside our house.
Well, not to fear.
Mister Cho here and I
will go back to your home
and see what we can find
to make your life easier.
- Yes!
- No, you don't have to do that.
- It's okay.
- I miss my dolls.
Not for long.
Thank you, both of you.
Shall we?
What's your play here?
I don't know what you mean.
What are you trying to do?
Bring a ray of hope
to a family, I suppose.
And help my friends
solve a crime.
I don't buy it.
You don't help us
because you like us.
I don't like you?
Well, you don't
not like us.
But you have deeper reasons
for helping people.
Without those reasons,
you're a hustler.
So what's your play?
You're wrong about me,
Mr. Cho.
I do like you.
And I can assure you I wanna
help that little girl
find her lost doll.
Okay.
What's wrong?
This doll.
It reminds me of something.
I can't, I can't quite..
It's your family?
Yeah, my family.
I can't believe I..
How could I forget my family?
I'm sorry.
Could you give me a minute,
please, Mr. Cho?
Sure. I'll wait outside.
[dial clicking]
[knock on door]
Jane?
[door squeaking]
Okay, if he does show up,
please call us right away.
Thank you.
He's not at the hospital.
I'm starting to get worried.
He has no money or ID.
Uh, yeah, he has money.
Found this in my wallet
when we got back.
"I owe you 60 bucks?"
Yet I'm $63 light.
He wasn't even honest
about that.
Let's start calling
local cab companies
see if any of the drivers
remember giving him a ride.
It's my fault.
I should know better.
So should I.
I'm the one who got him out.
We were all marks today.
Not me.
What? He didn't con me.
Only because he wants
to date you.
Really?
The death of Jane's family
made him a better person.
That person was always
inside of him.
The murder just
brought it out.
Rigsby.
Slow down. Who is this?
Are you drunk?
I do not do
spiritual readings.
You must have
the wrong number.
- No, stop! No, stop!
- Don't hang up!
Hello?
Where are you calling from?
Okay. I'm being pulled
in this direction.
There's an older woman, an aunt
or a cousin coming through.
There's a "K" connection.
A "K" connection
somewhere over here.
My mother's name
was Kate.
Twins. She's saying
something about--
What do you know
about twins?
I'm a Gemini.
That's your mother's way
of letting you know she's here.
She's letting me know it's very
important that you know.
'That you know
this is her opportunity'
'to make a connection.'
This is her chance
to come through.
[voice breaking]
Okay.
Your mother's saying..
...she was killed.
What I mean by that is..
hers was not
a natural passing.
Is that right?
It was a car crash.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Okay.
[inhales and exhales deeply]
That's how you lost her.
In a car crash.
'That's what you tell people.'
"I lost my mother
in a car crash.
I lost her. I lost her."
But what you're forgetting
is that she lost you, too.
'There is no greater loss
than a parent's loss of a child'
'but it's okay.'
'She wants you
to know it's okay'
'cause she's here with you.
'She's here tonight,
and she's telling me'
'that she wants a hug.'
A huge hug.
Come here.
come on, please.
Come on.
[applauding]
It's okay.
Oh, that's okay.
I hate him.
That's not him.
You're very brave.
You have a very
strong connection.
You won't lose that now.
Thank you, folks. Whoo.
[applauding]
Hi.
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
Business.
Excuse me. May I?
This is Rigsby's card.
Yeah, just you know until
I get my own printed up.
You said that you
were dying to help.
This is not helping.
I am.
I'm investigating. I felt bad
about the fish stunt
I pulled on these boys
so, uh, I decided to take
the "B" shift out
for a night on the town.
Make sure they're all
innocent of murder.
Are they?
They're the best of the best!
- Yep! Yep!
- You are the man, paddy!
- Thank you! Cheers!
- Cheers!
Oh, he got the last round.
Could you thank him for me?
We're going back
to the hospital now.
I'm gonna take a rain check.
I got another show later.
I'm best with the late crowd.
Are you gonna make me
call backup
to get you out of this bar?
Because I will do that, paddy.
Gentlemen
the best of the best!
- Yeah, buddy!
- Hey, paddy!
- Salute.
- Well said, my man, well said.
- Cheers.
[rock music]
I got it from here.
Thanks.
I'll see you in the morning.
Uh, no. Actually,
put a fork in it.
I'm done.
No more police work.
I understand.
You can stay in the hospital
until your fine.
What if I don't get fine?
I talked to my
paramedic friends.
All I need to be released
from this hospital
is the signature
from a responsible adult
and I got some
pretty tasty offers tonight.
[laughing]
And, this wedding ring--
I can make you stay,
you know.
It's in my power to hold you
as a material witness
in a murder investigation.
Why would you do that?
You think I can't see
what's going on here?
You people, you're,
you're tiptoeing.
You're dancing around
some forgotten tragedy.
I'm happy now. Just..
Just let me be happy.
Fair enough.
Look, I'll miss you,
but I'll leave you alone, okay?
Thank you, Teresa.
I appreciate it.
Any parting thoughts
on the murder?
Yeah, I figured out
who killed the fireman.
You did? Who?
Jacket left pocket.
Kind of obvious,
don't you think?
No.
Should I spell it
out for you?
Yes.
I suppose you need me
to gift wrap the killer, too?
You usually do.
Hmm.
My parting gift to you
I will give tomorrow morning.
Goodnight.
There's room up here.
Moving van, huh?
You have to put
a deposit down on that?
I thought you were broke.
Well, the investigation
is over.
They let me in the house
and I found our
emergency cash, thank god.
And now you're going away?
Montana.
No. Prison.
Put your game face on,
cockroach
for the dignity
of your family.
Hello there.
I got something for you.
I do.
Look at this.
Marcy-grace!
- Yes.
- Oh, that is so nice of you.
- What do you say, honey?
- Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
I found something else
in your house.
We have to get on the road
so whatever it is,
just keep it, okay?
Come on. Get in the truck.
Let's go.
Wait, what's this about?
Well, I don't believe
it's anything
your daughter
wants to hear about.
Honey?
[sighs]
Take her into the room.
Just go. I'll explain later.
It's okay.
Come on, baby.
Get crazy with
those cheese puffs, kid!
So cute.
Before I show you
what I found
I have to tell you
the story that goes with it.
Um, it's a tale of
an ATM robbery gone wrong.
I believe you read about it
in the newspapers.
Put the bags down!
'Do it!'
Now your guns. Slowly.
[Patrick]
'Well, I don't believe
the masked robber'
'intended to hurt anyone,
but then again, they rarely do.'
'The first thing
a smart criminal does'
'is destroy the evidence.'
'Fire, that's a very
popular way to do that.'
'With the fireplace alight,
the masked robber'
'ran upstairs to lock his stash
away in the bedroom safe.'
'What he didn't know
was the fire downstairs'
'was now burning
out of control.'
[coughing]
Excuse me, but what
does this have to do with me?
Bear with me.
It's been a rough week.
Now when the masked robber
found the bottom floor
of his house on fire
he should have
ran out.
[coughing]
'He couldn't abandon the cash,
not after all that.'
'So he ran back upstairs.'
'Problem is the smoke
was too thick.'
'He couldn't breathe.'
'The masked robber
passed out'
'right there
in his own bedroom.'
Are you accusing me
of armed robbery?
Yes.
And murder.
Oh, and, uh,
attempted murder, too.
Mine.
Well, you must
be desperate.
Hardly. I had you
pegged from the start.
You know how
armored guards operate
from your
savings and loan days.
And who would light a fire
on such a warm morning?
The hard part
was to figure out
what would drive you to kill
the man who saved your life?
'Then I realized that
firefighter saw something'
'when he braved those
flames to rescue you.'
I've got an unconscious
man in here.
[Patrick]
'Something that would
send you to jail for life'
'when he caught the news
reports of the robbery'
'and pieced together what he saw
inside that burning house.'
The mask. It had to be.
It's what you were trying
to burn with those bank bags.
It's what Satterfield saw
in your bedroom
and that's why
you had to kill him
[knife slices]
[grunting]
That's a scary story.
But without proof,
it's just a story.
Oh, almost forgot
the other thing
I found in the ashes.
Yeah.
I searched your house
before you did, remember?
I actually tried
to crack your safe.
It's not my specialty.
Don't worry.
I'm not here to bust you.
There's nothing in that for me.
I want half the money.
Half the money.
Well, I think
that's very generous.
I could ask for more.
What choice do youhave?
[clears throat]
[unzips bag]
Half.
Now the mask.
Uh, yeah. The mask.
Of course, yes.
You can have that there.
Wait. This isn't mine.
No. I found that
at a Mexican party store.
The colors are a good match,
though, don't you think?
Hands in the air.
Do it now!
[siren wailing]
Turn around.
[indistinct chattering]
I've always wanted
a couch like that.
Who's this?
Oh, this is my responsible
adult, Tamara.
Ta-mara.
Hi.
Well, you did it.
You caught a killer, and we got
back most of the stolen cash.
Most?
Wilcox was missing
some of the money.
He said you took it,
but we didn't believe it.
Hmm.
I'd look for an accomplice.
That's a big job
to pull off alone.
We'll do that.
Oh, by the way.
Your last paycheck.
That's my payment?
You weren't exactly
in it for the money.
I'll confess
to a vague satisfaction
in taking down someone
that thought they were
smarter than me.
But not enough
to wanna stick around here.
Alright. Well, let me know
if you change your mind
or, you know, get it back.
Some doors
are best left shut.
Uh, everyone else, I'd just
like to say thank you.
I'm sure we've shared
some great times together.
I'm not presently
qualified to comment,
so I'm just gonna make
like a rock and roll.
Bye.
Wait.
That looks real.
Sure does.
[chuckling]
Mmm.
Youweren't lying.
Huh.
You took it.
Wilcox wasn't lying.
You really took it.
I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm late for my new life.
When did you grab
the cash?
Oh, please,
does it really matter?
I mean, you people are
the highway robbers.
Look at this paycheck!
We could have you arrested.
No one can convict me.
I'm out of my mind.
Ask my doctor.
You're running away.
What are you talking about?
You're starting to feel
something inside
and you don't know
what to do.
That's nonsense.
Prove it.
Take a ride with me.
If you still wanna leave
after that, you can.
[car door closes]
Great house.
Whose is it?
It's yours.
Give me your keys.
Okay.
[keys jangle, lock turning]
[chuckling]
[slow instrumental music]
[music continues]
I'm sorry.